Shepherd 2, you're going too fast. Where are you right now?
シェパード２ 先行し過ぎだ
今　どこにいる
I can't find Hound 4... Sasayama.
ハウンド４が…佐々山が見つからない
What's going on? Where did he go?
どうなってる あいつはどこに行った
Calm down, Kougami!
落ち着け　狡噛
Things are getting out of control.
状況がつかめない いったん戻れ
Come back for now!
I'll bring Sasayama back!
佐々山を連れ戻す
Sasayama?
佐々山…
Dare ni mo miserarenai mono
My head is full of things
Atama no naka afurete
That I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
Machigai sae mo nai sekai he
I roam, a lost being
Mayoikonderu
Arienai hodo surikomareteru
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Me ni mieru mono dake no "sekai" genshou
Abakidaseru kana
Can I find its faults?
Plastic tac tic
Plastic, all is plastic
Mou dare mo okashiku narenai yo
Nobody is allowed to be insane
Kisama mo plastic beautiful world
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
Utsukushi sugiru sekai ni
Boku wa nazeka
There is something
Hikari ga mienakute
That obscures all light for me
Haretsu shite yuku kokoro ga
My heart tries to break out
And finds no answer
Mugen no rifurekushon
Secret kills for you
Secret remains for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
Misekake no iro to
Mirai wo abakanai de
Nor a world of pretense
Keep it secret motion
Keep our motion secret
#06: Return of
the Psychotic Prince
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 西西   校对:西西   后期:时末
Looks like she's working hard, huh?
頑張っている様子じゃない
She's still inexperienced, so she acts unprofessionally rather often.
まだ経験が浅い分 心得違いをしている部分も多々ありますが
But it's true that she's an excellent employee.
優秀な人材なのは事実です
I think she has a promising future.
将来的には有望かと
I hope so.
そうあってくれればいいが
There's still at least a chance she'll end up in an unfortunate state similar to that of your partner,
君の同期生のような残念な結末に至る可能性も 決してゼロではない
who started the same year as you.
Yes, Chief.
はい　局長
You Inspectors have very demanding jobs.
君たち監視官の職務は過酷だ
But you must keep a firm and unyielding spirit to pursue your duties,
多くの犯罪者 そして 執行官たちのゆがんだ精神と直面してもなお
even up against the distorted minds of criminals and Enforcers.
任務を遂行できる不屈の精神が必要なのだ
You should be on your guard too, Ginoza.
君とて油断は禁物だぞ 宜野座君
Science has yet to prove a causal
relationship between genetics and Crime Coefficients.
犯罪係数と遺伝的資質の因果関係は まだ科学的に立証されたわけではない
However, science has also yet to prove that there is no relationship.
だが裏を返せばまだ無関係だと証明されたわけでもない
I hope that you won't make the same mistake as your father.
君が父親と同じ轍を踏むことのないよう 心から祈っているよ
I hope it from the bottom of my heart.
I'll keep that in mind.
肝に銘じておきます
"In faith, they are as true of heart as we.
「本当の女心は決して私どもに劣りはいたしません」
We men may say more, swear more, but indeed
「確かにわれわれ男はもっと言葉にも出し誓いを立てたりもいたしますが
Our shows are more than will, for still we prove
本当は心にもない見せ掛けだけの場合も多うございます」
Much in our vows, but little in our love."
「私たち男は口先だけは立派なことも申しましょうが
愛情でそれを実証することがめったにございません」
Stop there.
そこまで
Yes, ma'am.
はい
The first performance of "Twelfth Night" took place in 1601.
『十二夜』の初演は１６０１年
In the sentences Kagami just read,
今加賀美さんに読んでもらったのは
you can get a glimpse of the astonishing universality of Shakespeare.
シェイクスピアの驚くべき普遍性が垣間見える文章です
Are you in literature class right now?
「そっちは文学の授業」
Yes. We're studying "Twelfth Night" by Shakespeare.
Yes.    We're                                 studying  "Twelfth    Night"
「はい シェイクスピアの『十二夜』です」
by Shak   espeare.
Shakespeare's comedies are boring.
Shakespeare's               comedies
「シェイクスピアの喜劇は退屈ね」
are boring.
You don't like his work?
You don't like    his work?
「お嫌いですか」
I do like his tragedies, especially
"Macbeth" and "Titus Andronicus".
"Macbeth" and "Titus Andronicus."
「悲劇は好きよ」
「特に『マクベス』と『タイタス·アンドロニカス』」
So those two are the interesting ones, huh?
「その２本が面白いんですね」
I do like his tragedies, especially "Macbeth" and "Titus Andronicus".
You don't like his work?
Shakespeare's comedies are boring.
Not only are they interesting, they're especially cruel.
「ただ面白いだけじゃない」
「特別に残酷なの」
cruel
But why aren't you looking it up in the database?
でもさ　何でデータベースで調べないわけ
You're an Inspector. You have authorization, right?
監視官なら権限あるっしょ
If I access those files, Kougami will know.
ファイル閲覧したら狡噛さんにバレちゃうじゃない
You don't want him to know?
バレちゃまずいわけ
Or are you that concerned about Ko?
つうか そんなにコウちゃんのことが気掛かりなのかい
Could this be love?
それって恋
Have you even been in love, Kagari?
縢君って恋したことあるの
Listen, Akane. I'm more experienced in life than you are.
あのね 朱ちゃん 俺ってば人生の先輩よ
Not only love. I've done all sorts of bad things.
恋どころか　悪い遊びは一とおりこなしてるんだぜ
I've glimpsed into a world that
a wholesome girl like you can't even imagine.
健全優良児の朱ちゃんなんて想像もつかない世界をのぞいてきたわけさ
Really?
For example, this one.
例えば　これ
Juice?
ジュース
No! It's alcohol. Real alcohol.
違う　酒だよ　本物の酒
Ol' Masaoka shared it with me.
征陸のとっつあんのお裾分け
These days, people are afraid of getting addicted to it,
今じゃみんな中毒性が怖いからって
so they stick to safe therapeutic tripping or go virtual, right?
安全なメディカルトリップかバーチャルばっかじゃん
That's for drinking, right?
それ飲むんだよね
Not for blowing fire?
火 付けるんじゃなくて
Say what?
ああ
No, nothing.
ううん　何でもない
Well, now's when we get to enjoy vices like this one.
まあ　こういういけないお楽しみも今じゃ俺らの特権ってわけ
I see.
Whoa! This is good!
おいしい
This is real cooking.
これが本物の料理ってもんさ
Hey, hey! I told you, those snacks are for drinkers only!
こらこら 酒のつまみだって言っただろ
Spoilsport.
ケチ
Or would you like to try?
それとも朱ちゃん試してみる
What?
If I get drunk, I might start talking about all sorts of things.
俺も酔ったら口が軽くなってしゃべっちゃうかもよ
The thing is...
だってよ 俺が採用されたときにはもうコウちゃん監視官降ろされてたからさ
When I started here, Ko had already
been stripped of his position as Inspector.
So I don't know the details.
詳しいことはよく分っかんねえし
Though I heard that an Enforcer who was under him at the time got killed.
何かそのとき コウちゃんの部下だった執行官が殺されちまったって話だけど
Killed?
殺された
Right. He was going after a culprit, but ended up as a victim.
そう 犯人追っ掛けてたはずが 逆に犠牲者になっちゃったのさ
If I remember correctly, his name was Sasayama.
確か佐々山とかいったっけか
He was killed in the same manner as
the other victims. I heard it was terrible.
他の被害者と同じ手口で  そりゃもうひどいもんだったらしいよ
So it messed Ko up and his Crime Coefficient went way too high.
それで コウちゃんおかしくなって 犯罪係数ぶっちぎっちゃって
That case was never solved, but Ko's still investigating it.
あの事件迷宮入りって話だけど いまだにコウちゃん調べ続けてるらしいよ
I see...
そうなんだ
Anyway...
つかさ…
How can you drink so much and still be okay?
朱ちゃん 何でそんな酒強いわけ
You just get drunk too easily.
いや　縢君が弱過ぎ
Enforcer Sasayama?
佐々山執行官
Ah, there's no way I could forget the Specimen Case.
そりゃ忘れられるわけないわ 標本事件は
Specimen Case?
標本事件
That's how we, and the detectives, referred to the case.
私らや現場じゃそう呼んでたんだけどね
Do you know what plastination is, Akane?
朱ちゃんプラスティネーションって分かる
It's a process used to create biological specimens, right?
生体標本の作成方法でしたよね
Right. It's a technique for preserving tissue by impregnating it with resin.
そう　死体に樹脂を浸透させて 保存可能な標本にする技術
So, in the Specimen Case, this process
was used to commit grotesque murders.
あれを活用した猟奇殺人だったのよ
They first dismembered and cut open the body,
バラバラに切り開いた遺体をプラスティネーションで標本にして
and then they used plastination
to turn it into a human specimen.
Then they brought it right into the middle of town and displayed it...
そいつを街のど真ん中に飾りつけてくれたわけよ
underneath a Holographic
illumination used in the entertainment district.
盛り場を飾るホログラフ·イルミネーションの裏側にね
How terrible...
ひどい
Thousands of passersby thought they
were just looking at environment Holo.
何千人という通行人が環境ホロを眺めているつもりで
But in truth, there was a dismembered body right underneath it.
実はその下に隠れてるバラバラ死体とご対面してたっていう…
When that got out, the area stress jumped up four levels.
バレたときのエリアストレスは４レベルも跳ね上がってね
It was so bad that they even imposed a news ban.
報道管制まで敷かれたほどよ
あっ…あの食事中にすみません
I'm sorry I asked about it while you were eating.
Huh? What're you talking about?
うん　何が
Yayoi wouldn't get worked up over something like this.
弥生はこの程度じゃ燃えないわ
She's into more violent and passionate stuff.
もっと激しくて 情熱的なのがお好みよ
Um...
えっと…
You guys were talking about the Specimen Case, right? Go on.
今は標本事件の話でしょ　続きは
Well, since it was obviously done by an expert,
まあ　明らかに専門家の仕業だったからね
the investigation focused on experts in pharmacology and chemistry.
捜査の焦点も 薬学、科学のエキスパートに絞り込まれていったんだけど
But then, Sasayama was killed while working on the case.
その途中で 佐々山君がね…
In the end, while investigating a totally unrelated report regarding a missing high school teacher,
結局 全然別件で捜索願の出てた高校教師のアパートから
they came across plastination resin in his apartment.
プラスティネーションの樹脂が見つかってね
See, this guy. Touma Kouzaburo.
あっ　ほらこいつ
藤間幸三郎
Right after he went missing, the crimes stopped,
こいつが失踪した途端に犯行も止まったし
so there's no doubt he was the culprit.
まあ　間違いなくクロだったはずなんだけど
But all we had was circumstantial evidence.
状況証拠だけだしね
So in the end, it remains an unsolved case.
まあ　実際のところは迷宮入り
In addition, Touma didn't know anything about chemistry,
それに藤間には科学の素養なんてなかったから
so even the question of who created the resin remains a mystery.
問題の樹脂を誰が調合したのか それさえも謎のまま
Does that mean that there was an accomplice?
共犯者がいたってことですか
I don't know if we can really call them an "accomplice"
そもそも用途を承知の上で樹脂を作ったのかどうか
when we don't even know if they
understood what their resin would be used for.
それすらも分からないんじゃ 共犯と呼んでいいのやら
It remains a mystery as to how it was acquired too.
入手経路も謎のままだし
At this point, God only knows.
今となっては神のみぞ知る よね
Looks like you're having a rough time as usual.
相変わらず 苦労してるみたいね
う～ん　分かる
You can tell?
Considering how gloomy you look, it'd be hard not to.
そんな陰気な顔してれば 一目瞭然だっての
Being on the fast track is tough, huh?
出世街道も大変よね 守秘義務が　多くて
You have to keep lots of things confidential.
Exactly. It's hard.
まさに　そのとおりで… つらいよ
Is this still about that erratic colleague of yours?
相変わらず 例の　危なっかしい同僚の件
I still don't know what to make of him.
もう　ずーっと 振り回されっぱなしなんだけど
What's more, it seems like he was once in the same position as me.
しかも　その人　昔は　私と同じ境遇だったらしいんだよね
Don't tell me this troublemaker used to be an honor student
まさか そのトラブルメーカーも昔は優等生で
whose test scores were over 700 or something?
考査のポイントも７００オーバーとか
Right! That kind of thing!
そう　そんな感じ
This is just a thought, but...
もしかしてだけどさ…
Yeah?
うん
Could it be that you and your subordinate are quite similar?
あなたの部下と　あなた本当は　よく似てるんじゃない
What?!
It's urgent! I gotta go!
急ぎの仕事　行かなきゃ
Hey, we just got here!
って まだ　会ったばっかりじゃん
I'll make it up to you next time!
今度　埋め合わせするから
It seems that Kuzuhara Satsuki is still missing.
葛原沙月さん 行方不明のまま 帰ってこないみたいだね
I've heard the teachers have been ordered to keep silent about it
教員たちにはかん口令が敷かれてる
so as not to worry the students.
生徒たちを不安がらせないようにって
Why?
何でそんな…
That worries us even more.
余計不安になるじゃない
The selling point of this school
この学校ってさ つまりは多感な思春期の少女を社会から隔離して
is that they keep girls of susceptible age
isolated from society in a conservatory environment
in order to prevent their Psycho-Passes from getting cloudy.
サイコパスを曇らせないよう温室栽培するってのが売りなのよ
So they sweep problems under the rug.
だから臭いものにはふたをする
They also need to keep up appearances in front of our parents.
保護者相手の体面もあるしね
Oh no, I'm scared!
やだ　怖いよ
There are some other rumors that are pretty scary too.
怖い噂だけならもっとあるよ
One of the teachers who used to teach in this school was actually...
昔この学校にいた先生の１人に　実は…
Miss Ouryou!
王陵先輩
It's Miss Rikako!
璃華子さまだ
I wonder why Ouryou Rikako is so popular.
王陵璃華子って何であんなに人気があるのかな
She's pretty, she's smart...
美人だし　頭もすごくいい
It's pretty obvious.
理由ははっきりしてるじゃない
I'm a little afraid of her.
私　あの人ちょっと怖いんだよね
Why?
どうして
Sometimes her eyes just look so empty.
目が…ね
時々うつろなんだ
It's as if...
ここじゃない　別次元を見詰めるような目をする
they're staring into a different dimension.
Kawarazaki. Shimotsuki.
川原崎さん　霜月さん
Hi.
どうも
H-Hello.
こんにちは
Sorry to interrupt your lunch.
食事中にごめんなさい
What brings you here?
何でしょうか
Neither of you belong to any clubs, right?
２人とも何のクラブにも所属していないでしょ
Educational organizations that have club
activities like our school, Ousou Academy,
ここ桜霜学園のような クラブ活動をやっている教育機関なんて
are very rare these days.
今ではすごく珍しいの
I thought it'd be a shame to miss out.
もったいないと思って
Are you recruiting us?
勧誘ですか？
Oh, you figured it out!
バレちゃった
I'm the president of the art club.
私　美術部の部長をやっているの
If you'd like, please come and see us in our club room.
よかったら部室に遊びに来てね
Also, Shimotsuki...
あと霜月さん
I sometimes get absorbed in thought,
ぼんやり考え事をすることはあるけど
but it's not like I'm looking into a different dimension.
別次元を見ているわけじゃないから
I'm not an alien, you know.
宇宙人じゃあるまいしね
You dummy, Mika! She heard you!
美佳のバカ！聞かれてたでしょ
Sorry.
ごめん
Pardon me.
失礼します
Thank you for coming.
来てくれたのね
I heard about your father.
聞いたわ あなたのお父さまのこと
Your mother's new husband.
お母さまの再婚相手
So you took... notice of it?
気付いてて くれたんですか
Yes, since I've been watching you all this time, Yoshika.
ええ　私はずっと葦歌さんを見ていたから
Miss Ouryou!
王陵先輩…
Will you tell me what happened?
何があったのか 話してくれる
That man... he...
あの人はその…私のこと はっきりといやらしい目つきで…
clearly looks at me... with...
o... obscene eyes.
Every time I go home, there's signs that someone was in my room.
家に帰るたびに
誰かが私の部屋に入った跡があるんです
I can't stand it anymore... but...
こんなの耐えられない
でも…
You can't talk to your mother, right?
お母さまには相談できないのね
The debt my biological father left us is so big
本当の父が残した借金は
that my mother couldn't hope to repay it by herself.
とても母だけでは返済しきれなくて
So we have to depend on that man.
あの男に頼らないと…
But at last week's regular check up, my Psycho-Pass was very cloudy.
でも先週の定期健診でも
サイコパスの色相すごく曇ってて…
If I don't do something...
このままじゃ私…
Yoshika.
葦歌さん…
It seems you can't choose the life you wish.
あなたはあなたが望むとおりの人生を選べない
I understand how hard that is.
そのつらさは分かるわ
In this era, the System determines everyone's aptitudes
今の時代 誰もが システムによって決められた適性に沿って
and we all have no choice but to live by it
and be satisfied with whatever "happiness" is forced upon us
押し付けられた幸せだけで満足するしかない
as we are unable to make our real dreams come true.
自分が本当に望んだ夢を かなえることもできずに…
Don't you want to discover the person you desire to be?
本当に望む姿 本当の自分の価値
Don't you want to realize your true worth?
それを確かめてみたいとは思わない
What?
I can show you...
私なら教えてあげられる
the true beauty that's hiding inside you, Yoshika.
葦歌さんの中に隠れている本当の美しさを
Shall I tell you more about Shakespeare's works?
シェイクスピアの話 続きをしましょうか
Yes.
はい
"Titus Andronicus"...
『タイタス·アンドロニカス』
The character I like in it is Titus's daughter, Lavinia.
私が好きなのはタイタスの娘ラヴィニア
She got dragged into trouble because of her father.
父のせいでトラブルに巻き込まれて
The enemy raped her,
彼女は敵に性的暴行を受け 舌を切り取られて
cut out her tongue
and cut off her arms as well.
両腕も切断される
"It was my deer..."
「これは俺の命より大事なカワイイ子鹿だった」
Poor Lavinia.
かわいそうに…
She was killed by her own father.
ラヴィニアは自分の父に殺されるの
There are tons of things that humans can do but animals can't.
人間にできて
動物にできないことが 山ほどある
One of them is safety control.
そのうちの１つが安全制御だ
No matter what it is, humans have always put a safety device on it.
人間はどんなものにでも 安全装置を付けてきた
Enforcers are also equipped with a safety device called Inspectors.
執行官にも監視官という安全装置が付いている
More to the point, the drones you controlled were equipped with rigorous safety controls.
君が操ったドローンには
特に厳重な装置が付いていた
Those drones were supposed to be completely safe,
絶対に安全だったはずのドローンに
and yet, this memory card made them kill people.
殺人行為を実行させたメモリーカード
Where did you obtain it?
君はどこで入手した？
So we have the safety canceller that
Kanehara used in the Hachiouji Drone incident
八王子のドローン事件で金原が使ったセーフティー·キャンセラーと
and Midou's Holograph cracking.
御堂のホログラフクラッキング
In both cases, I could only recover a bit of the source code,
まあ　どっちのソースコードもほんの断片しか回収できなかったんだけど
but there are clear similarities.
明らかに類似点がある
I think the same programmer wrote the code for both.
同じプログラマーが書いたって線に
I'd bet the bra I'm wearing today on it.
私は今日着けてるブラジャーを賭けてもいい
You can keep it!
いらねえよ
It's true that Midou was obsessed with social networks,
御堂は確かにソーシャルネットのマニアではあったが
but he wasn't skilled enough to mess with public Holo.
公共のホロに干渉できるほど 高度なハッキング技術はなかった
There's no doubt that both Kanehara and Midou
were being backed by a professional cyber-criminal.
金原も御堂も電脳犯罪のプロからバックアップを受けていたのは間違いない
But this testimony of Kanehara's isn't going to help.
しかし肝心の金原の供述がこれじゃあな～
I'm telling the truth! I just got it one day in the mail!
「本当だ！ある日いきなり俺宛てに郵送されてきた」
The letter had no name or return address.
「送り主の手紙には名前もなくて
It just said that it was from
someone with a grudge against that factory
ただ　あの工場に恨みがあるから一緒にめちゃくちゃにしてやろうって！」
who wanted to mess up that place together with me!
That's pretty vicious for someone
who'd commit crimes just for kicks, isn't it?
愉快犯にしては悪質ですよね
How could the sender predict that
Kanehara would kill in the first place?
そもそも金原が殺人を犯すと
送り主はどうして予測できたんだ？
Pops figured out Kanehara just by checking the records of the staff's periodic checkups.
とっつあんも職員の定期健診記録だけで 金原に的を絞ったんだ
There was someone else who could do the same thing.
同じマネをできるやつがいた
That periodic checkup record wasn't confidential, either.
あの診断記録は部外秘だったわけじゃない
Then what was this guy's motive for helping Midou?
じゃあ　そいつが御堂を手伝った動機は
It was Kanehara and Midou who had the motive.
動機は金原と御堂にあった
That must've been enough reason for him.
やつはきっとそれだけで十分だったんだ
Kougami?
狡噛？
The intent and means to kill...
殺意と手段
To create a crime by bringing those
two otherwise separate things together.
本来揃うはずのなかった２つを組み合わせ 新たに犯罪を創造する
That's his goal.
それがやつの目的だ
Tsk.
Hey!
おい
Kougami, what are you doing?
狡噛　お前は…
Gino, this is the same as that case.
ギノ　あの事件と同じだ
There's someone who seeks out those who have
not yet found a way to manifest their desire to kill,
ただ殺意を持て余していただけの人間に手段を与え
and grants them the means to become real killers.
本当の殺人犯に仕立て上げてるやつがいる
Calm down and think about it.
落ち着いて考えろ
Back then, it was a special resin.
あのときは特殊樹脂だが
This time, it was a tool for cracking software.
今度はプログラムのクラッキング?ツールだ
They're totally different!
全然違う
Public Safety Bureau
Special Case 102
The engineer and the middleman are two different people!
技術屋と周旋人がまた別なんだ
There's someone who brings together those who want to kill
人を殺したがっている者と
and those who can create the tools they need to do it.
そのための道具を作れる者とを引き合わせているやつがいる
That's the real mastermind.
そいつが本当の黒幕だ
Enough already!
いいかげんにしろ
You're chasing a ghost that we don't even know exists!
お前はいるかどうかも分からない幽霊を追い掛けているんだ
Sasayama was on the brink of figuring it out.
佐々山は突き止める寸前までいった
I'll settle this for his sake.
あいつの無念を晴らす
That's what I've spent the past three years working toward!
そのための３年間だった
This is Takahashi from the Public Cleaning Bureau.
清掃局の高橋です
I'm at the Central Fountain Tower right now.
中央噴水塔の前なんですが
Noise has been appearing in the Hologram for a while now.
ずっとホログラムにノイズが出てまして…
Yes, that's right.
はい　そうなんですよ
Please turn off the fountain Holo so that we can check it out.
確認のため 噴水のホロの停止をお願いします
What's that?
何だ？あれ
Whoa! That's creepy!
気持ち悪い！ 人形か？
Is that a doll?
Is it some sort of artwork? A sculpture?
何か美術品とかじゃないっすかね
Yeah... but isn't this in kinda bad taste?
でも悪趣味過ぎないか
Who the hell did it?
まったく誰だ
But...
でもよく見たらすごいリアルっすよね
When you look closely, it looks pretty real, doesn't it?
It's quite elaborate.
凝ってんな
Though I wouldn't want to display it at my home.
まあさすがに家に飾りたくはないけど
Do you think Lavinia was happy...
辱めを受けた命から解放されて
having been freed from her violated body?
ラヴィニアは幸せだったと思うかい
"Because the girl should not survive her shame,
「娘が辱めを受けた後も生き永らえ
and by her presence still renew her sorrows", was it, Mr. Makishima?
その姿をさらして悲しみを日々新たにさせてはなるまい」
でしたっけ？槙島先生
Even beautiful flowers must eventually wither and fall.
美しい花もいずれは枯れて散る
That's the fate of all living beings.
それが命ある者全ての宿命だ
If that's how it is,
ならいっそ咲き誇る姿のままに時を止めてしまいたいと思うのは
it's only natural that one would wish to freeze
them in time while they're still blossoming in full glory.
無理もない話だね
But if you really loved her as if she was
your own daughter, would you too say...
だがしかし　もし君が彼女を実の娘のように愛していたというのなら…
"Kill'd her, for whom my tears have made me blind", as Titus did?
君は「あの子のために流した涙で盲目になって」しまうのかな？
Oh, that'd be a problem...
あら　それは困りますわ
because I still have many more drawings to complete in the future.
だって私
これからももっともっと新しい絵を仕上げていかなくてはならないんですもの
Fearii teeru wa
It seems all fairy tales
Sakki shinda mitai
Are dead
Renga no byoutou de
In a hospital ward of brick stones
Umaku utaenakute
My voice is too coarse to sing
Kiri ni kemuru yoru
Outside in the foggy haze
Ukabe akai tsuki
A red moon glows
Hora mite watashi wo
Look at me
Me wo sorasanai de
Do not avert your gaze
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
Behind black bars
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I was born
Behind black bars
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
Akui no daishou wo negae
I wish there were a punishment for evil
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Always I need you
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Now, grant us justice
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Before chaos takes us all
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Namae no nai kaibutsu
Nameless beasts
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Nameless beasts
Namae no nai kaibutsu
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".